Everybody has a secret...
She's the Man is a comedy, romance film directed by Andy Fickman.
Viola Hastings is in a real jam.
Complications threaten her scheme to pose as her twin brother,
Sebastian, and take his place at a new boarding school.
She falls in love with her handsome roommate, Duke, who loves
beautiful Olivia, who has fallen for Sebastian!
As if that were not enough, Viola's twin returns from London ahead of schedule but
has no idea that his sister has already replaced him on campus.
Viola, played by Amanda Bynes.
Duke, played by Channing Tatum.
Olivia, played by Laura Ramsey.
Dinklage, played by Vinnie Jones.
Gold, played by David Cross.
Daphne, played by Julie Hagerty.
She's the Man is a 2006 American romantic comedy teen sports film directed by Andy Fickman and
starring Amanda Bynes, Channing Tatum, Laura Ramsey, Vinnie Jones, and David Cross.
Inspired by William Shakespeare's play Twelfth Night, the film centers on teenager Viola Hastings, who enrolls at her brother's
new boarding school, Illyria Prep, in his place and pretends to be a boy in order to play on the boys' soccer team.
She's the Man emerged as a moderate commercial success, grossing
$57.2 million against a budget of $20–25 million.
The film received mixed reviews from critics, but Bynes's performance
was universally praised and developed a cult following.
The film explores themes of high school, sports,
boarding school, roommates, twin sister.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.